# Angie Washburn

7841 Dawson Drive, Fishers, IN 46038 | 317.579.0124 (Home) 317.625.1959 (Cell) | angiewashburn1997@gmail.com

# .NET Developer

Professional with more than 25 years of experience in various areas of business, education, and the medical fields. Experience includes: organization, project management, fund raising, data collecting, reporting, event planning, system development, beta reading, beta testing, customer service, and patient care. Skilled in areas of process improvement, reporting, quality, attention to detail, and thoroughness. In addition, currently a participant in .NET program at Eleven Fifty Academy learning HTML, CSS, jQuery, JavaScript, and C#. Using tools such as Visual Studio, GitHub, and Sublime Text.

- Strong understanding of HTML and CSS.
- Familiar with JavaScript and C#.
- Experience with beta testing and bug reporting.
- Proven customer service skills.
- · Worked within Visual Studio IDE.
- Training in Agile methodologies.
- Teaching and training experience in various environments.

## **Experience**

#### CONTRACT HOME CARE | CLARITY CARE, FISHERS, IN | AUGUST 2015-PRESENT

- · Assist with needs of geriatric patients in home setting.
- · Manage daily tasks through Clear Care System.
- $\cdot\,$  Keep staff and family updated on patient status.

# CONTRACT ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT | KELLER WILLIAMS EVELO TEAM, INDIANAPOLIS, IN | OCTOBER 2014-DECEMBER 2015

- · Assisted with errands and data entry.
- · Managed daily expired listings.
- · Visited properties as necessary.

#### **STAY-AT-HOME MOM | 2001-2015**

- · Raising three children.
- · Maintained schedules and managed household.

# EMPLOYER SERVICES ASSISTANT/RECRUITING COORDINATOR | BALL STATE UNIVERSITY CAREER CENTER, MUNCIE, IN | 1997-2001

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Coordinated recruiting activities between employers and students.
- · Created and maintained systems for on-campus interviewing.
- · Created tools for sharing data with staff via Access databases.
- · Recorded job line.
- · Assisted with job fairs.
- · Hosted employer visits.
- · Awarded Customer Service Award four times.

# Angie Washburn

7841 Dawson Drive, Fishers, IN 46038 | 317.579.0124 (Home) 317.625.1959 (Cell) | angiewashburn1997@gmail.com

#### SENIOR SOFTWARE SUPPORT ANALYST | MASTER SOFTWARE CORPORATION, INDIANAPOLIS, IN | 1995-1997

- · Assisted customers via phone and onsite with software installation and troubleshooting.
- · Tested and bug reported on newly developed software.
- $\cdot\,$  Presented at conferences.
- · Wrote specific documentation for clients.
- · Awarded Customer Service Award multiple times.

#### ADJUNCT FACULTY | INDIANA BUSINESS COLLEGE, ANDERSON, IN | 1998

- · Developed lesson plans and taught evening computer class.
- · Created interactive learning environment.

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

- · The Julian Center, Indianapolis
- · Trinity Free Clinic, Carmel
- · IU Saxony Hospital, Fishers
- · New Britton Elementary School, Fishers—President PTO (2013/2014)
- · MOPS (Moms of Preschoolers), Anderson and Fishers
- · Fishers High School, Fishers—AP and IB Exam Proctor (2014 and 2015), President-Fast Break Club (2015/2016)
- · Dale Carnegie, Indianapolis

#### Education

# BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | DECEMBER 1994 | BALL STATE UNIVERSITY, MUNCIE, IN

· Major: Business Administration

### GENERAL MEDICAL CLASSES | 2006 | IVY TECH COMMUNITY COLLEGE, INDIANAPOLIS, IN

· General classes

#### ASSOCIATES DEGREE | MAY 2010 | INDEPENDENCE UNIVERSITY, SALT LAKE CITY, UT (ONLINE)

- · Major: Respiratory Therapy
- · Clinical Portion: St. John's Hospital, Anderson, IN (2008-2010)

#### .NET TRACK | 2016 | ELEVEN FIFTY ACADEMY, CARMEL, IN

· Coding Education and Experience

### REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST.